[
  {
    "question": "Who is the leader of 369?",
    "options": ["Elon Musk", "Diovan Stark", "Brema Banner", "Euphoria Romanoff"],
    "answer": "Brema Banner"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 369's fanbase called?",
    "options": ["Circle", "Pi", "Orbit", "Thor"],
    "answer": "Pi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Diovan Stark's specialty?",
    "options": ["Physics", "Biomedical Engineering", "Computer Science", "Winning hearts without trying"],
    "answer": "Computer Science"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the most reticent in 369?",
    "options": ["Lawrence Rogers", "Cupcake the beagle", "Tom Musk", "Cassandra Lang"],
    "answer": "Lawrence Rogers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which color represents 369?",
    "options": ["Pink", "Blue", "Green", "IDK, maybe rainbow?"],
    "answer": "Blue"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Qubits does TriQ has?",
    "options": ["36.9 million", "3.69 billion", "Infinite, BOSS!", "369 billion"],
    "answer": "36.9 million"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which gadget harnesses black hole energy?",
    "options": ["SingularisDrive", "EnerHole", "My hunger", "SpaceFold"],
    "answer": "SingularisDrive"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Panacea V?",
    "options": ["Victory chance determiner", "Self-evolving nano-vaccine", "Pancake recipe", "Schwarzchild radius calculator"],
    "answer": "Self-evolving nano-vaccine"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tech was used to reprogram damaged neurons in NeuroRegenesis?",
    "options": ["Tiny glue bottles", "CRISPR-Cas9", "ASI", "Thermal microwave"],
    "answer": "CRISPR-Cas9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tech 369 invented to make air fresh?",
    "options": ["0Carb", "CarciNo", "CarbonEraser", "CarbonDIY"],
    "answer": "CarbonEraser"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the parent company of 369?",
    "options": ["Stark Tech", "Tesla", "IBM", "T&S Institute of Advanced Sciences"],
    "answer": "T&S Institute of Advanced Sciences"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of 369?",
    "options": ["Dr. Victor Vortex", "Satya Nadela", "Dr. Maya Hawke", "Vladimir Putin"],
    "answer": "Dr. Victor Vortex"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is half Russian in 369?",
    "options": ["Brema Banner", "Cedric Thorson", "Tom Musk", "Euphoria Romanoff"],
    "answer": "Euphoria Romanoff"
  },
  {
    "question": "How old were 369 members during inception?",
    "options": ["12", "15", "14", "10"],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which AI was built by Diovan Stark?",
    "options": ["J.A.R.V.I.S.", "D.E.L.T.A.", "F.R.I.D.A.Y.", "D.A.R.K."],
    "answer": "D.A.R.K."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which platform 369 uses officially to take online classes?",
    "options": ["YouTube", "InnoSphere", "GoTeen", "Google Classroom"],
    "answer": "InnoSphere"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the youngest member of 369?",
    "options": ["Diovan Stark", "Euphoria Romanoff", "Brema Banner", "Tom Musk"],
    "answer": "Diovan Stark"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who discovered Swiftium?",
    "options": ["Cassandra Lang", "Euphoria Romanoff", "Brema Banner", "Tom Musk"],
    "answer": "Cassandra Lang",
  },
  {
    "question": "Tom's cheese crackers are from a ___ brand.",
    "options": ["American", "Swedish", "British", "Italian"],
    "answer": "Swedish"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I say, I'm just here to ___.",
    "options": ["eat", "enjoy", "experiment", "entertain"],
    "answer": "entertain"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the name of Euphoria's lion?",
    "options": ["Emily", "Eden", "Eric", "Phoenix"],
    "answer": "Eric",
  },
  {
    "question": "How many triangles are there in 369's logo?",
    "options": ["1", "3", "7", "4"],
    "answer": "4"
  }
]
